aralifestyle.com 2010-06-27

# Privacy Policy

##  ARAlifestyle.com Privacy Policy

**Welcome.**   At ARANet, Inc, the company that operates ARAlifestyle.com, we are committed to protecting the online privacy of visitors to our websites. This Policy applies only to the information collected through ARAlifestyle.com. The purpose of this Policy is to inform you about the types of information we gather about you when you visit our websites, how we may use that information, and how we disclose it to third parties. Your use of this website is also subject to our Terms and Conditions. 

**Site Not Intended for Children.**   Our website is intended for a general audience and are not intended for use by children without their parent's / guardian’s supervision. We ask that anyone under the age of eighteen not submit any personal information through our websites. We do not knowingly collect any personal information from children under the age of eighteen. 

**Links and Advertisers on This Site.**   This website contains links to other websites, including to sites operated by advertisers that are clients of ARAlifestyle. We provide these links for your convenience, but we do not review, control, or monitor the privacy practices of other sites. We are not responsible for the performance of these sites or for your business dealings with them. Your use of other web sites is subject to the terms and conditions of those sites, including the privacy policies of those sites. Please note that we may allow third party advertisers to place ads on our pages. Those ads may include cookies. Our advertisers' use of cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this Policy. 

**Personal Information.**   This Site is not designed to collect any personally identifiable information about you. Although the Site may include a page for businesses to contact us about advertising opportunities, this page is not intended for use by individual consumers. Providing such contact information is purely voluntary and is not necessary to view any article on this Site. We use contact information in order to contact a person in response to their request for advertising information. 

**Non-Personal Information and Cookies.**   When you visit our Site we collect certain non-personal information from your computer. This information is collected from your computer’s web browser and may include information such as the following (“non-personal information”):

-   the type of web browser software you use (for example, Internet Explorer)  
-   the name of the domain from which you access the Internet (for example, Yahoo.com)  
-   the date and time you access our websites, as well as which pages were viewed

We and/or our advertisers or vendors may also place a text file called a "session cookie" in the browser files of your computer when you visit. “Session cookies” are not loaded onto your hard drive, and do not give us any personal information. You are always free to decline our cookies if your browser permits, but some parts of our websites may not work properly for you if you do so. 

We will use non-personal information to help us make our websites more useful to visitors and for other business purposes. We may use information from cookies to deliver content that you may find more interesting based upon the articles you have viewed in the past. We may prepare reports and other materials using non-personal information. We may share and use non-personal information without restriction because it does not identify who you are. 

**Data Processed in US.**   By providing any information to us through this website, all users, including without limitation users in the member states of the European Union, fully understand and unambiguously consent to the collection, storage, forward transfer, and processing of such information in the United States of America. 

**Contact Us.**   If you have questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at [info@aranetonline.com](mailto:info@aranetonline.com) or send us a letter addressed by First Class Postage Prepaid U.S. Mail or overnight courier to the following address:

Privacy Officer, ARANet, Inc.  
701 Fifth Street South  
Hopkins, MN 55343

This Policy was last updated on March 10, 2010. We reserve the right to change this Policy at any time, and will post any changes to this Policy on this page or a similar page of this website as soon as they go into effect. Please refer back to this Policy on a regular basis.
